<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flynn Walsh&#39;s site on flynn&#39;s site</title>
    <link>https://flynns.site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flynn Walsh&#39;s site on flynn&#39;s site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 03:00:53 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://flynns.site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Dough</title>
      <link>https://flynns.site/recipes/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:21:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flynns.site/recipes/pizza/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (per ~12&amp;rdquo; pizza):
 75g all purpose flour 75g 00 pizza flour (all purpose can be substituted) 5g salt 100g tap water 2g olive oil 1g yeast  Procedure:
 Mix all ingredients in a large bowl, working until thoroughly combined. Let rest 15 minutes, then knead another 2 minutes. Rise 2-3 hours, divide if necessary, and shape.  Dough lasts in the fridge for a day and weeks if frozen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Abby Cake</title>
      <link>https://flynns.site/recipes/dear_abby_cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flynns.site/recipes/dear_abby_cake/</guid>
      <description>Cake Makes two moist and chocolatey 8&amp;rdquo; cake layers.
Ingredients  3 oz. unsweetened chocolate (total 4 oz.) 1/2 cup butter (total 9 tbsp.) 1 cup water 2 cups cake flour (sifted) 1.25 tsp. baking soda 1 tsp. salt 2 eggs (total 5) 1 cup (8 oz.) sour cream 2 cups sugar (total 3 cups) 1.5 tsp. vanilla (total 3 tsp.)  Procedure  Preheat oven to 350 F. Melt 3 oz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://flynns.site/rpg/d12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flynns.site/rpg/d12/</guid>
      <description>The Simple d12 System Philosophy Simple d12 is a minimalist, setting-agnostic, abstractly realistic system. It is designed for ease of character generation and minimal player downtime. Combat is authentically fast-paced, rushed, and lethal.
Character Generation   Determine a setting-appropriate background, consisting of a character&amp;rsquo;s:
 upbringing, including:  nationality social class   education (formal or informal, if any) previous endeavors (if any)  e.g. military service      Select a vocation, specialized to the period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sourdough Recipe</title>
      <link>https://flynns.site/recipes/sourdough/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flynns.site/recipes/sourdough/</guid>
      <description>This 75% hydration, 15% whole wheat loaf draws from a mix of this King Arthur recipe and Ken Forkish&amp;rsquo;s Flour Water Salt Yeast.
Ingredients:
 300g 100% hydration starter (e.g.) 700g all purpose flour (I use King Arthur flours) 150g whole wheat flour 600g room temperature water 22g salt  Procedure:
 Feed starter 4-6 hours before mixing&amp;mdash;if starter is kept in a mason jar, it should be just about overflowing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>